right so I'm starting a new 90-day
challenge because I am watching a new
series of videos by Kyle sees and he
always inspires me to do things like
this
I mean like he basically tells you
things like this so my 90 day challenge
is going to be one hour of time of day
so 30 minutes of meditation 15 minutes
of yoga five minutes of play go which is
an envisioning exercise and ten minutes
of videos so I'm not gonna come on for
ten minutes I'm gonna sit and plan for
five minutes and then come on live for
five minutes because I want to keep
sharing myself for I am reason I put 90
days in quotations as I also know myself
with my anxiety and everything else I'm
not gonna let this go because my anxiety
comes up because that's what I'm sharing
I'm sharing all of it my idea is my my
journey all of it but sometimes it stops
sparking joy so I'm gonna do a 90 day
video challenge I might switch over to
this other thing on Twitter at some
point during that 90 days to talk about
this project like it's already happened
in 2028 because that's what my twitter
twitter my twitter Twitter feed is why
that needs to be repeated Jacob to you
so me
I am Jubilee I am a single mother to a
amazing six-year-old and I have various
health challenges ten mysteries and life
circumstances so which together would
combine on me being on disability
full-time I don't work at all hate work
had two tons of work like everyone else
especially women I'm a housebound most
of the time with limited energy but in
that space I've been able to remix the
knowledge it was already in my head and
went on this interpersonal journey that
I'm still on it's still ever changing
and growing and on that interpersonal
journey I switched from this space of
like oh I can't contribute and I feel
isolated and alone and useless - what
can I do from here with my limitations
with where the world is like what is
here and I have
points so I have clearly I'm sure them
like from being in my house not able to
go out a lot of the time to dealing with
my brain which is both extremely
stubborn and altered
I have damaged here and I'm like I'm not
talking about it like it's brain damaged
anymore my brain was altered through the
course of radiation and brain spelling
after surgeries and it's changed and
dealing with my current level I have
pain and fatigue all the time and also
comes a brain fog some more fun brain
changes I have a medical need for a
stress-free life I also am dealing with
the world that all of you live in too
so this level of what the world is
capable of like where we currently are
and where our current technology is what
our current capacity is that's what I'm
working with and what can I do from here
not like what does society say I need to
do and I'm not living up to a bit like
what can I accomplish from here it's
this I could hit record on a video for
five minutes
I can show up as I am I can do amazing
things and the thing that i remixed in
my head is what I'm creating is the
Netflix of apps but with and for the
mass of the masses of users so we are
gonna run it democratically and
transparently it's not gonna look like
anything that's been done before this
isn't Google this isn't Facebook this is
our technology company our apps that are
all gonna work together to make all of
us live a better life instead of having
to trade a human hour to get although
that will happen to you can't all have
house cleaners because who cleans the
house cleaners houses but we can all
have like self cleaning toilets we can
all have a personal assistant that is an
Android right the org iPad our own
version which ever that we can all have
used technology to live a better life so
basically what I'm creating is is sorry
for the wording that triggers people but
like socialism but within the framework
of capitalism so that it's voluntary
and it will only succeed if the ideas we
come up with are better if they can
actually out-compete what is available
currently in capitalism this isn't about
creating a subpar product that then we
force our members to use the point is to
create something beautiful and
functional that works for purpose
instead of profit and works together and
we have all these efficiencies of our
own little monopoly because we are
creating it for ourselves we're not
creating it to sell it to users the user
is the member and we're all gonna run it
and own it and do everything together
it's getting to that point and so I will
introduce our first project which is
what I'm looking for people to work on
maybe it's my last video maybe in a
different video are you dealing with day
by day I'm not planning out the whole 90
days I am doing this day by day so I
will come on tomorrow probably around
the same time I'm trying to do them
first thing in the morning if I wake up
before my kid